<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Seasoned Tech</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Seasoned Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Untitled. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Seasoned Tech</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Seasoned Tech, your partner in navigating the complex world of technology leadership and innovation.&#xA;Our Mission At Seasoned Tech, we believe that every company, regardless of its size or industry, deserves access to top-tier technical leadership. Our mission is to provide executive-level tech expertise on demand, helping businesses overcome challenges, seize opportunities, and achieve their technology goals.&#xA;Who We Are Seasoned Tech is the brainchild of Evan Williams, a veteran software engineer and technology leader with over four decades of experience in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Evan Williams</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/biography/</guid>
      <description>A Journey Through Four Decades of Tech Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/services/</guid>
      <description>Services Offered: CTO for Hire MVP Development Legacy System Modernization Technical Strategy Consulting Project Rescue and Turnaround </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/faq/</guid>
      <description>FAQ:&#xA;What types of companies do you work with? How long do typical engagements last? Can you scale up resources for larger projects? What&amp;rsquo;s your approach to project management? How do you ensure knowledge transfer at the end of an engagement? </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
